I have asthma. Back off!
"Riddle me this.
Arrah, Arrah, and gather round,
(Howard:)the work of this hero
is legion-bound.
(Howard:)He multiplies N
by the number of He,
(Howard:)and in this room
the thing you'll see."
(Raj:)-Good riddle, huh?
-Yeah.
(Stuart:)So when you guys plan fun activities,
does my name even...
Come up, or...?
(Raj:)I invited you to my
murder mystery party.
(Stuart:)-No, you didn't.
-Oh.
(Penny:)We're the last ones here,
hurry up!
(Sheldon:)-It is a marathon, not a sprint.
-People run in a marathon!
(Sheldon:)Not with a bowling ball
on their back.
(Leonard:)Hey, Penny, I just
wanted to say good luck,
and I hops there's no hard feelings.
Hey, Romeo! Repair your relationship
on your own time!
(Leonard:)Relax, it's a hard puzzle.
It's gonna take a while to solve.
-"Riddle me this--"
-Got it.
(Penny:)Hey, Princeton, look at that,